(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T12:08:50.805259",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
We miss her!
It's been two weeks since we saw her!
She hasn't left her room in two weeks.
She doesn't love us anymore!
Is that... Jailboss?
Tonight, we infiltrate her bedroom. Follow me, I know a secret passage.
You dare enter my room?!
What the?!
Don't mess with the girlfriend!
Aw...
生まれたばかりの赤い花
Born into the world, a deep red flower
只、孤独にゆらゆら
Just alone, swaying in the wind
解答の無い檸檬
Without any answers
弁明は脆く愚かな結末
An excuse, a fragile and foolish conclusion
磔にされた心は泣いている
The heart nailed to a cross is crying
両手から落ちるこの滴が
These drops falling from both hands
貴方には見えていないのでしょう
You probably cannot see them
なら此処まで
Then, that's it
悲しい声に、コトバに、追いかけられて
Driven away by sad voices, by words
頷いたまま微笑む赤い花
A deep red flower that smiles while hanging its head
深く根を張る痛みが贖いなら
If the pain that roots deeply is atonement
解り合えない　ずっとこのまま
We cannot understand each other, always just like this
変わらない定め真理は不条理
The unchanging fate, the truth is absurd
剥き出しにされた感覚の違い
The difference in sensation that has been laid bare
風の吹く夜に
On a windy night
散ってしまえば花の色彩を
The color of the flowers that wither and scatter
貴方は知ることもきっと無いのでしょう
You will surely never know
底の底まで堕ちたら黒い景色
If I fall to the bottom of the abyss, a black landscape
頷いたまま泣いていた赤い花
A deep red flower that was crying while hanging its head
朽ちていく心の中まだ願っている
Deep inside the decaying heart, I am still wishing
ありのまま生きていたいと
That I want to live as I am
悲しい声に、コトバに、追いかけられて
Driven away by sad voices, by words
頷いたまま散りゆくアネモネ
ANEMONE that scatters while hanging its head
深く根を張る痛み（いじ）が無くても
Even if the pain that roots deeply does not disappear
もがき続ける　何度だって
I will continue to struggle, no matter how many times
淡い想いに手を伸ばして
I will reach out my hand to the pale memories
Little darling,
My love, where are you?
Hello, are you over here?
Ah,
Oh, there you are! My darling!
Oh, you look so cute laying on my bed like that.
Isn't he just adorable?
I just want to squeeze him, but I'll leave him be for the time being.
Jailbirds, I have to welcome you to my room, as this is a very, very special day.
Do you know? Do you remember that today is my birthday?
In case you don't know me, let me quick introduce myself.
In case you don't know me, let me quickly introduce myself.
Hiya darlings, this is holoLive English Advent's
devilish diva, the only Nerissa Ravencroft,
and I'm so happy to have you in here for my room debut.
Being able to celebrate with you guys is so amazing,
but I thought it'd be more fun with friends here.
Would you guys please come on in?
What's up, you fuckers!
Leave them alone!
We're here for your cat!
No, you're here for me, right?
For me!
Wait, look at your bed!
Oh, happy day! Celebration!
Nerissa! Yay! We're here!
We're here for your cat!
No, you're here for me, right?
For me!
Wait, look at your bed! Uh, yes!
What do you guys think, by the way?
It's just like you!
I'm glad. I want to show off some details,
I know you guys have been here before, but this is the jailbirds' first ever time seeing my room.
So, let me go ahead and point out some of the details.
First, because everyone's so interested in it, I want to highlight the bed area.
In this area we have a lot of my personal plushies
and my cat. He does have another cat bed when he likes to sleep there.
It's also very princessy, right? Just like me, right? Baby girl coded.
I also have a beautiful painting right above my bed. And I see something else there. Is that a jailbird? No, no way!
That's not a jailbird, right? Uh, who knows?
Then behind me, over behind Fuwamoco, there is this beautiful vanity area. It's my kind of... it makes me feel even more princessy.
You can see there's a bust of my head because you got to bust me. It's important. It's important.
I also have a renaissance painting scattered throughout the room, too. You might notice them. I have little Advent references.
There's a Pero hiding, some are over here.
Up there I have a Novalite, and then over here, over by the vanity area, there's a little Gio.
Lots of little Advent references all around for you to enjoy.
So yeah, that's it. That's awesome, right? That's it. All right, time to leave!
Well, thanks for having us! Thanks so much, we're leaving now!
Yeah, you're leaving? What? We're not leaving! I saw your cat! I mean, okay.
So, are you going to have us do anything then while we're here? Yes!
Well, I prepared a very special game today, actually. I think you guys are going to have a lot of fun.
It's something a little out of the ordinary. A tattoo? Yes.
So today you must treat me like your princess.
Well, like your princess, actually. No, no, your princess, and you are my princess.
So, it's going to be a blind date. You have to make my heart flutter a lot, and make me feel amazing on my birthday.
I guess it'll be fun then.
I'm the... I'm the one being rissed in this game. I'm excited to see your unexpected sides.
So, uh, I need to prep everything in my room, so I need you all to get over there. Just over there. I'm going to set up everything, okay? In the corner.
Okay, I'm going to set up.
Wait, what if we go around? I'm setting up. I'm setting up. Are you supposed to get dizzy like this? I'm going to pull everything, okay?
You're supposed to be here! I'm just getting dizzy. Yeah, it's just don't worry, it's just the furniture is a little heavy.
Spin her around! Spin her around!
I have everything already! Okay.
Okay, what do you guys think?
Wow, a chair? It kind of doesn't match the room's theme, though.
It's fine.
I'm going to be sitting in this chair right here, and I'm going to put on a blindfold too.
Oh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait! Don't worry, don't worry, don't worry!
We'll put pianas on this projector. Pianas? What? Pianas? Pianas? Pianas?
You guys can relax, okay? Relax! And come close to me, you're so far away.
So, on this projector here, there's going to be prompts with various questions,
and situations will appear, so you all have to answer them one by one.
Your voices are going to be altered with a voice changer.
Oh! Why? Is it going to be cute?
Yeah, but I'm not going to be able to know who's talking.
So, based on that, I won't have any pre- preconceptions about anyone, because it'll just be based on your rizz alone.
So, based on that, I won't have any preconceptions about anyone, because it'll just be based on your rizz alone.
So, feel free to be extra romantic, okay?
What's that, Shiori?
Don't worry about it.
We'll do our best to be romantic then, huh?
Let's start! The name of the game is Cellmate's in Love.
The questions for everyone will be displayed on the projector screen, so please read them carefully.
But I must put my blindfold on now.
Oh. Oh. Oh.
Okay, so I guess he won't know who's answering, so the person should move quietly so she doesn't know the order.
Okay, so I guess she won't know who's answering, so the person should move quietly so she doesn't know the order.
Yeah.
And plus we have a voice changer.
Okay. Okay, well, we should probably line up now, huh?
Okay. Who wants to go first?
I don't know. How about I think you should go first?
Okay, we'll continue answering in this order then. Yeah.
Okay. Huh? Now, give us the first question!
It's been over two years since Rissa and I became friends... But I think it's time to take our relationship beyond friendship! I'm scared I might ruin what we have... But... I really want to tell her how I feel!
So, you gather your courage and finally decide to ask Rissa out on a date! What would you say to ask her out, and where would you like to go for your first date? Try to ask her smoothly!
Oh.
But I'm scared I might ruin things.
But I also really want to tell her how I feel.
So, everyone, gather your courage, and finally decide to ask Rissa out on a date!
What would you say to her, and where would you like to go for your first date? Try to ask her smoothly!
That was a lot.
Okay, so it's not just a hypothetical situation, right? So on point, isn't it?
We all have to figure how to ask her out. You know, considering I how you are now, right?
While you're ready, then. Okay. Bye!
Right here! Okay.
Nerissa...
You know, I've been thinking...
You're really important to me, and I'd like to go out somewhere special together, and I... Maybe have some time.
Just the two of us, you know?
So, I was thinking, maybe we could go to that cafe that you said you liked a few months ago. Oh, your favorite, right? Ah, we could go there and have a nice evening, and then maybe...
You know, once our tummies are all full, then we can go on a bit of a stroll. Enjoy, you know, the city lights, maybe the water.
What? Would you like that? I would like that! That sounds so sweet!
Well, then, it's a date. Okay.
Let's do it.
So romantic. Okay.
I did my best.
You did great.
Okay, good job, good job.
I'll go. I'll just go. I'll do your best. I go. Yeah.
Show her what you're made of. Hey, I can wear the necklace a little bit for me. I mean, I don't think you need that.
No, you'll be with love. You could, but...
This is kind of mean, isn't it? Whatever. Deal with it.
Oh, hey, I'm ready. I'm ready.
Hey, Nerissa, you and me, movies tonight.
Calm or don't. But if you don't, you're going to miss you're going to miss out so much, baby.
You know, we're going to do the movies, we're going to pick the scariest movie ever, and then...
I'm going to be such a beeping wimp.
I'm going to cry,
I'm going to cringe at the jump scares. I'm going to be so beeping scared you're going to have to comfort me.
And then you're going to have to put your arm around my shoulder and you be like, "It's okay, sweetie, you'll be fine."
And then I'm going to—I'm going to nuzzle myself into your chest, yeah, while you comfort me, and we're going to bond over fear.
And it's going to be the most amazing thing ever.
What is this? Oh my gosh, that sounds...
Come to the movies with me, or not. It doesn't matter.
That sounds so enthralling!
I know. Whoa. I'm kind of interested. It sounds like a booty call.
But I'm—I'm a little scared too.
I feel like I'm—I'm going to have to be the one comforting you, and I don't know how I feel about that. That's a point. Yeah, that's—that's a point.
Well, that's a good... Okay, let's move on to the next person then. How about...
That was a good job.
Nice try!
Next person. Who's next?
When I tell you that you're done...
well, you have to go—I forgot that you have to show off.
Yeah. Get going! Going!
And I'm waiting. That sounds pretty good. Impressive. Yes.
Well, so... um... well, you know,
you've been close for a little while now.
And, you know, we've never really been able to hang out just the two of us, you know.
And so, I think I really like it, you know, just you and myself, and so I was thinking,
maybe we could go... I got a massage together, and then afterwards, once you feel so much more relaxed and free,
we could go to a café—a café that's really special to me, uh, because I know you're a little indecisive too.
And then we could just chat on more.
More? Oh! That sounds so fun, too!
You guys are really speaking to my—to my heart here with these cafés and dates and stuff.
I like it a lot. I think we have one more contestant.
So, contestant number four, will you please take the stage? Yes! Make it romantic!
Stomps angrily on the ground.
I would go on a date with you.
No, thank you!
My lady, tips Fedora, pulls out ten million dollars in cash,
waves it under your nose. This is all for you.
And you know what? Not only that, but I have ten million roses in the ground right here!
They all don't die, just like my love for you. That's how it's supposed to be. You're as beautiful as the moon, and so bright, so elegant, so in the night sky. I love seeing you at night, man.
Sorry, what are we doing for this date?
Oh, sorry! I forgot about the date! Going on a date would be dope.
Okay, you've convinced me.
I think all of you have successfully managed to Rizz me on a date.
So, there's our first question.
Yay! Come on back, come on back.
Let me get my cash again. It just drops so much.
I can't tell who my favorite is yet. I think we're going to need some more questions for me to be able to pick.
What? There's more? Yay!
All right, well, let's move on to the next question then.
All right. You successfully asked Nerissa out, and she happily said yes!
Since it's your first date,
you want to make her feel special and happy.
What kind of surprise would you like to plan for your first date?
Of course!
Well, what kind of surprise do we have in store for our first date?
A surprise!
Yeah! Lots of surprises!
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, the question is, are we going to continue the story of our first dates?
Yeah?
Oh, uh.
Maybe, uh.
Let's do that! Me? Okay!
Okay. Blindfold back on.
Okay. Yay!
All right, I'm ready to be Rizzed.
All right. Well, let's go. And we're ready to Rizz you.
Let's go in order of Rizz, then.
Okay, that means...
Do I go?
She's so brave!
So then, doing our date while we're walking along the water at night with all the city lights around us,
suddenly, you elucidate me.
Huh?
Well, let's see, huh?
You feel a bit panicked, and then suddenly,
you see a bunch of mascot characters,
and they're doing a little bit of a dance, like...
And then, all of a sudden,
one of them goes, 'Whoa!'
And out comes me!
A bit of a surprise! And, uh, I have roses,
and I say,
You're the character of my life.
For you.
So cute!
That's so romantic!
Bachelor number one!
Thank you!
Romantic, yeah.
Okay.
So good.
Thank you!
Yes!
All right. Next up, let's go.
Go on, my little Rissa champion.
Oh hey, guys, is that you?
Still, the mic is okay, well, whatever.
All right, Nerissa, after our date, you know,
um,
you have to take me home, because
I spilled my drink all over myself
from being scared 'cause you were comforting me, right?
Uh so, afterwards, I you take I take you home to my place.
Uh, so afterwards, I take you... I take you home to my place.
And you know what we're going to do?
We open the door, and there's trash everywhere.
And that is my surprise,
because I know everything about you, and I know that you love cleaning.
So, surprise! My room is dirty
and you have to clean it,
and you love that so much!
And that's so romantic for you, I'm like, 'Yeah, woman, clean my house.'
And, and I let you, I let you clean my house
And I let you... I let you clean my house,
and you'll feel so strong, you know that?
You know, I do love to clean,
especially for my friends.
However, I think if I was on a romantic date,
it would not be at the top of my list.
But, but in, in the trash there is like treasures for you that I put,
But in, in the trash there are like treasures for you that I put...
I put in the trash, like flowers. There's like, there's flowers,
and you have, you have to dig for...
and you have to dig for...
I think I would be turned off by that.
I feel like when I found them, I might be like, 'Oh, that's cute,' but I, I, I might be a little...
I feel like when I found them, I might be like, 'Oh, that's cute,' but I might be a little...
You did your best.
So let's move on to the next one.
How about that?
That's good. No one understands me.
That's the type of romance. It's okay.
Okay. Okay, who's next?
Did you like it? Good job. Good job.
I gotta do my best!
You know, here at this cafe,
I guess they're really excited for the cake that we ordered, right?
And well, I wanted to surprise you,
and I know there's one thing that you love very much. So...
Nerissa, look at me in my eyes.
You see this here?
This is my smartphone. Slam! Slam on the table!
Today, I'm giving you
all my attention,
because you're my princess,
and today, it's just you and me.
Whoa, the rest of the world disappears
when we're together for you. That's such a good surprise!
I love it so far! Bachelor number three!
All right, let's hear the last bachelor, shall we?
That was a good one.
Yeah. I'm sad, I'm sad.
My lady, as we walk on the moon
where our date takes place in,
I reconstructed it from the ground up,
there is an amusement park
in your honor, in your name,
Nerissa Ravenland.
And there are jailbirds
as far as the eye can see,
and you, each one serves you to the utmost ability they have,
they have, you can even step on them, that is my surprise.
You can even step on them. That is my surprise.
An entire army just for you, a fat flocks.
An entire army just for you, a fat flock.
Oh my gosh, that is kind of romantic.
Yeah. But I think they do that for me regardless,
I don't think I need...
What?
They're moon jailbirds.
They're moon jailbirds?
They're moon jailbirds? It's like a whole different species.
They're moon jailbirds? It's like a whole
different species.
Are they like white colored, too, then?
Yeah, they're also maybe fatter.
Yeah, but not on my love for you.
What?
You feed them with your love?
That's how they survive.
Well,
thank you, bachelor number four.
No problem.
That was awesome.
These are all awesome dates.
Well, it was mine.
Ooh.
Well, it was a good attempt.
Good job, everyone, yes! Let's move on to the next question, shall we?
Heart-stirring line
[Title: Heart-stirring line]
...even on this special date, you'll feel frustrated that your "just friends" vibe has not gone away yet!
Um, now you want Nerissa to see you more than a friend, and you want her to think of you as like a more of like a romantic interest!
So it's time to make your move! Say something to win or heart!
Please do win my heart, Advent!
Please... Don't look! Is that possible?
Yeah, I'll put my blindfold back on and you guys can come up with everything you want to say!
Well, thinking time's over, Bachelor number one, would you please approach the mic?
Say something... Say something to make her more than friends!
Always so serious. Bachelor number one, Bachelor...
Go, Bau Bau! Let's go!
Um... I'm Bau.
Bau?
Nerissa, you know, we've spent a lot of time together.
Um... I think I know you pretty well, and I would hope that you would think the same of me, but...
I feel like, you know, I'd like to take things a step further. You know, we're not just friends anymore, right?
So... Can I... Can I hold your hand? Ooh! Please, princess, you can... you can hold my hand...
If you want to... I'll... I'll hold your hand. Oh. That's enough!
Thank you! That's so sweet! Hand holding?
That's such a big advancement of our relationship, but I'd still like to hear Bachelor number two!
Cos, look! Look at this! You got it? Look at this.
You trust the story! Go, William!
I'm William.
All right, babe, let's go over here.
Ooh! Is this consented?
You hear me in your ear, right? Yeah. Hold this. Smell me right now.
Do I smell like trash? Do I smell good? I smell good too.
That's the pheromones, babe. That means you're attracted to... If you think I smell good too, that means you like me so much. You're so attracted to me, so I think we should take our relationship to the next level. What do you say?
You're too close! Is that a yes?
Baby, I... I kinda love...
I enjoy that aggressiveness a little bit, I think.
Yeah. It's... It's nice. But...
Data corruption: invalid timecodes or overlapping segments
Yeah, you got... You got to have this one. Definitely. Yeah, but it's...
Maybe just a little forceful. Maybe just a little sudden. 'Cause in your dirty... in your dirty room with all your dirty trash and your dirty flowers underneath the... I don't know.
Like I feel like it might be a little bit disgusting. But it's just you, and maybe in the moment you'll forget about everything.
I see. Well, let's move on to Bachelor number three.
You can do this.
You can do it.
What? What's her name? Go, Matilda! Matilda!
Matilda? Why was I Bill?
Why not?
Nerissa, we had some very nice times together this year and me...
And, well... No, we're Jamies. But to me, we're a lot more than that.
You know, every time I send you one of those pictures that, um, maybe some doofus do that, let's just me and you... There was a reason behind that.
And, well, today I'd like you to know that. So, um, I'm waiting for your answer, okay?
Cute! It's so innocent, too!
Thank you, Bachelor number three. Good job.
All right, we have just one bachelor left. Bachelor number four, will you take the mic, Steve?
Steve, you've gone...
Bill, William, Matilda, and Steve... I was always such a kidder.
Nerissa, my dearest, I like you more than a friend.
Even... I don't know how you feel about me.
And regardless of who you choose, whatever makes you happy, I will honor it and I will hope that you will always be happy with that person, whether it is the beautiful Matilda...
And regardless of who you choose, whatever makes you happy, I will honor it and hope you'll always be happy with that person, whether it's the beautiful Matilda...
...the other people I've named, I forgot I've named. You're just so wonderful and your smile is precious.
...or the other people I've named—I forgot I've named. You're just so wonderful and your smile is precious.
Tips fedora... walks away with my 10 million dollars of cash depending on how you answer.
Tips fedora... walks away with my $10 million of cash depending on how you answer.
Oh my gosh!
So sweet!
That's so earnest! Too wait, I wasn't expecting that from you, Bachelor number four, Steve!
That's so earnest! Wait, I wasn't expecting that from you, Bachelor Number Four, Steve!
No one ever expects that with a person with 10 million dollars.
No one ever expects that with a person with $10 million.
I know.
Well, how sweet, you guys all did so good! I feel my heart racing for sure.
And so, which one made your heart skip a beat the most, huh?
Well, beyond this dancer of who made my heart... stop!
With the bachelor number two! That's pretty good, yeah.
But I don't... it's difficult to say.
I'd take that as win.
I'd take that as a win.
Yeah, it's pretty good. It's difficult.
Again, it's still hard to pick. I think we have to ask a few more questions before I can settle on one of you.
One more! Yes. Two more questions. So, shall we read off the next one?
Okay, let's go to the fourth question then! Okay. Okay.
The sweet days you longed for with Nerissa...
It's been two years since you finally confessed your love, two years...
...and embraced something truly special between the two of you.
Everything seemed perfect, like a dream you never wanted to end.
But a tiny mistake on your part sparked a huge fight between the two of you!
With all your heart, apologize for the wrong you've done, and strive together to overcome this trial that threatens your love!
Okay, got it. So we've been dating for two years, and you guys have upset me. Twice is...
Okay, got it. So we've been dating for two years, and you guys have upset me twice. So...
So, won't you please apologize and make it all better? I'll put my blindfold back on. So make things right between us, okay, you four?
Won't you please apologize and make it all better? I'll put my blindfold back on. So make things right between us, okay, you four?
Huh?
Two years? Two years is pretty serious. It's un-usable.
Two years? Two years is pretty serious. It's un...
All right, bachelor number one, it's your turn.
Okay. Here I go.
Nerissa... I'm sorry.
I know I hurt you very deeply, with all my... Well, it wasn't meant to be like this, but ultimately, it turned out this way.
My indecisiveness, my lack of action...
I know that you, the love of my life...
I should have done it. I should have already proposed to you. Already have made you long before, but...
I'm sorry for hurting you this way, for hurting you at your core, in your heart so deeply. Could you ever forgive me?
What a cutie! Still, bachelor number one, you managed to be so earnest and sweet.
You're really reaching to my heart. Let's move on to bachelor number two and see what sort of answer they're going to give.
Such a champ!
Yeah!
Hey Nerissa. I know I was gaming with the boys, and you walked... you walked in, and you wanted attention.
And I was like, 5 minutes, I can't pause the game, it's an online game, Nerissa!
And then you went and went crying. But after the gaming session, I was like, hmm, maybe I did do something wrong.
Maybe I should have... maybe I should have invited you to play a game with me.
So, I'm going to do something that I've never done ever once in my life. I've never done this before. I apologize.
Never apologize to anyone ever. And I'm going to apologize to you now, so listen.
Sorry, I guess.
You want to be my player two?
I'll play with you instead of the boys.
Why? Come here, baby girl.
I think that's good, bachelor number two.
Let's move on...
to bachelor number three. That she loved that.
Thank you.
All right, bachelor number three, to the mic, please.
Hey.
I know things have been a little weird recently, huh?
I wanted to say something.
Nerissa...
I'm sorry.
I know... you know... maybe I was acting a little childish.
I kept on saying things...
like...
"You're stinky."
You know, maybe you took that personally, but...
it was just... I was teasing you.
Because I love you.
I love you, Nerissa, way beyond words. I'm sorry.
And I just wanted to say is that... you're stinky.
But... I love it. I love your stink.
That's enough! Let's move to the last bachelor, bachelor number four.
Nerissa...
It's me, one of the boys.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry that...
the other person and I were gaming instead of-
We were just having so much fun playing games together.
I should have been focused on you.
I'm crying right now.
'Cause I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry as one of the boys.
This is your feeding apology.
Thank you?
I guess in your universe, I have two boyfriends.
I'm dating both you and bachelor number two. I forgot for that too, by the way.
Nerissa, I forgive you.
Oh, very very understanding lover.
Well, I think I'm getting closer to my answer of what one of these lovely bachelors I'm going to pick, but I think we're going to maybe need one one more question. One more. Okay.
Wow! Let's move on to the final question. And after this one...
Nerissa makes her decision about who she chooses.
So, Nerissa, please answer carefully, okay? From the heart, okay? From the heart. Yeah, in fact,
Rissa, why don't you read the final question so you can finally see?
Okay.
Question number five.
My Eternity.
This is your moment, bachelors. Make the ultimate marriage proposal to me!
I've never made a marriage proposal before!
Marriage proposal?
Now's the time. So, let me put my blindfold back on, and I'm looking forward to seeing your answers. Or hearing them.
Two years and she still can't see us.
You know, a marriage proposal, should we really be going to the mic?
Oh, I guess you guys can do whatever you'd like. Bachelor number one, will you approach?
Slow, thinking.
Bachelor number one, do not love me or something?
Where are you? It's such a special day. We've been out to dinner at my favorite restaurant.
Are you standing me up on such a special day?
Um.
Nerissa, will you craft?
Yes.
What's so funny?
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Will you marry me? Yes!
Shisaria! Shisaria!
Yeah!
I mean, we've been dating for two years.
Or meow mean.
We're getting married with Bachelor number two.
Is that it? It's over?
Yeah.
Boom. I tossed something on the ground, pick it up.
I know you're blindfolded, pick it up anyway, pick it up.
Wait.
Go.
Oh my god!
What is going on?
It was a ring. I put a ring on your finger.
We're engaged!
It looks like...
Hey, that's the wrong hand!
That's the wrong hand!
I love berry you!
Get out of here!
We're berries!
That was so scary!
I'm so scared!
You gotta go comfort her now.
Please no more harassment, bachelors!
Let's move on to bachelor number two... or three!
No more bachelor number two, bachelor number three, please!
You've crossed oceans across...
It's been many seasons that have passed since we met.
Many memories, hard times, beautiful times.
Many tears we shed together while watching the sunrise.
I'd like to spend many more sunrises and sunsets together.
Would you be my everything?
Yes.
Oh, that's so sweet!
Bachelor number three!
You're so sweet!
I don't feel like I should clap.
All right.
You don't have to.
We have one more contestant, bachelor number four, would you please approach?
My bro.
Yes?
You are like the broest of my life.
Wait, what the heck's going on?
Thanks.
We've been gaming for like two years or more.
Yeah, bro, we have been. I know.
I love playing farming games with you.
I love playing shooting games with you! You are my number two, or my number one even. I'll be your number two!
Hello? What?
Yeah. I just love you so much, my bro.
Oh, thanks, bro.
Yeah.
Will you marry me?
Well, I think I'm disqualified. Yeah! Bachelor number four!
Get out of here! Get out of here!
We're berries!
And with that, the questions are through.
We've had some awesome love's... awesome, maybe, if you can call it that, love stories born. Some good, some bad.
From one to four, which guy did you like the most? Please review the numbers.
Who was the most romantic? I'm... I'm gonna go backwards, actually.
I think it's... it's obvious which bachelor did not steal my heart today.
Okay, drumroll, drumroll. Bachelor number two, step forward! You're disqualified!
Bachelor number four, step forward! You're disqualified!
Bachelor number three, step forward! You're disqualified!
Somehow, I feel like I knew it was you two. I don't know what you're talking about!
Come on, wifey.
This is the hard part now. I'm between bachelors number one and bachelor number three. Who stole my heart the most?
Was it the earnest bachelor number one, or the very sweet bachelor number three who seemed to know me best?
Ah, I can't decide! But if I had to pick between this impossible decision...
I'd have to pick bachelor number three!
Okay, pig! You can join me! We're married!
We're married! We're married! I love it!
But I must say, knowing that each of you thought so deeply about a life with me—except some of you, maybe—
it makes me feel so special on my special day. So thank you for warming my heart.
Congrats! Yay!
Yay!
Happy birthday, I guess!
What a wonderful birthday this is!
I've even found a wonderful partner!
It feels like this next year of my life is going to be so amazing!
I know! My baby!
Hey, the blind date's over!
It's time back to reality! Oh, let's play Twister!
I got Twister ready so we can all play together!
Looking at it, it might be a bit tricky for all five of us to play at once, though.
Yeah, I think you might be right.
What should we do then?
Um... Well, how about to make it fun, we can play one at a time?
You know what, actually, I've just thought of a special rule for today. Let's call the game Posing Twister!
As the name suggests, the rule is to strike poses while playing Twister.
For example, if the instruction says, "Right hand on red" and "Cat pose," you place your right hand on red and do the cat pose.
Once all four limbs are in position, you can move just one limb to strike the specific pose.
The time limit will be one minute, and if you can keep your balance for the full minute, you can clear the challenge. But if you lose your balance at any point, the game is over.
Quick question!
Oh, yes?
Can the audience mess with the player?
Uh, yeah, why not?
So...
Who wants to go first?
What?
Well, we were just playing some video before so...
Yeah!
I guess I'll go first! Okay, Doki-de-pass! I'll show you how it's done, okay?
I'll try my best to strike two poses!
All right.
I've never played Twister before. This is my first time, then.
Well, okay.
You got one minute, okay?
Do your best.
We ready?
Then let's start!
Go!
Okay!
Left foot on green, wolf pose!
Okay, next!
Right hand on red, cat pose!
Wait, fast poses! Right hand, faster, faster!
Cute!
Left foot on blue, cow pose!
Cow! Cow! Cow!
Yeah!
All right! Right hand on red and hero pose!
Wait, right hand is hero!
Yeah, I thought my right hand is on red.
Right hand on red again! I can't help it! It is right hand! Hero pose! Hero pose! Hero pose!
Left hand on yellow, happy pose!
So happy!
Now, place your left foot on yellow and express anger!
I'm furious!
So much anger!
Mad pose!
You did so good!
If you do that, it feels like I could split apart!
Hai! Hai!
You did so good! All right, Moco-Co!
You passed with flying colors!
Don't fall, you can!
Don't fall, okay?
All right!
Who's next, Moco-Co?
Um, well, you get to choose.
Biboo!
Biboo's next because you made fun of me at the beginning!
Yeah! Do it! Do it!
Because of that, I'm going to be your biggest distraction, okay?
How about I tell Biboo what to do then?
Okay!
All right, let's start!
Right foot on blue!
Okay.
Now give me a graceful queen pose!
Oh my!
Left foot on blue, now do a lion pose!
Left hand on red!
Give me a rabbit pose!
Rabbit? Left hand the rabbit say-
Figure it out, I'm not a rabbit!
Let go! Let go!
Now place your right foot on green,
and go BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
Left foot on red,
now give us your best grr pose!
Grr! Grr!
Right hand on blue,
okay? Now kawaii, go kawaii!
Kawaii dance! Kawaii, kawaii yoroshiku ne!
Good enough for me!
You win! You win!
You're going to lose your balance!
But I didn't think that was a very cute pose at the end. What about you guys?
Well, you didn't win,
but you did your best so good job, me!
Okay, good job.
All right, you pick who's next, Bibe.
Uh? Okay, Shiori, you go next.
Okay, tell me what to do.
All right, boss me around!
Okay, Shiori, are you ready?
I guess so.
Let's start!
Left foot-
Yeah?
Put it on yellow!
Yellow, got it! And now you're going to show us- baby Shiori?
Baby Shiori! Okay, no! Again! Left foot on yellow!
Left foot on yellow!
And- Always horses!
And neigh! More horse! More horse!
Okay, next is right hand on blue!
Got it! And now- Give us your-
Coolest prince pose! Will you marry me then, there?
Okay, let's stop this. Right foot on yellow!
Witch pose!
Okay, and witch pose!
This- This is my broom somewhere here.
Hey, hey, there's a broom here! Okay!
Now, your left hand on red!
Okay, and do a bear pose!
I am already in bear pose. Grr!
Okay, you're going to take my hand and put it onto yellow!
Okay? And you're going to do a butterfly pose!
I am wiggling like a butterfly!
I am flying! I am flying!
Good job, Shiori!
You did so good, Shiori! You did so good at this!
Well, Shiori, wow, you're so good at this!
I know, I don't know.
You'll do great!
Well, Fuwawa, I think you're up!
Okay! I don't know if I'm going to be-
You're going to be good! My foot's going to touch you!
Okay, who am I going on?
Okay! Do your best now!
Pup-pup!
Okay, let's start!
Okay, right foot on green and do a hula dance move!
Right foot on green? Yeah, right!
Okay. Woo! Hula! Hula! Okay, okay!
Left foot on yellow for a dolphin pose!
Oh no, they need water!
Very funny! Dolphin! Dolphin!
Okay, next, right hand on red, fighting pose!
Right hand on red! Good luck! Good luck with that!
Ah! I can't! Oh no!
You can do it! Great, great! You can do it!
And don't fall yet! Go, go!
Oh, you have to get it! You have to get it! Careful with your foot!
Oh, your foot! Your foot! Your foot!
Right foot on yellow, puppy pose!
That's your default! You can't take your hands off! Let you weep!
Hi. Then right foot- Your cheer. Right foot! Right foot!
Bow-wow! Bow-wow! Okay!
Well, that's going to have to do. You're great! And that's so cute!
You know, it was really good. Oh, so cute, puppy!
All right, Nerissa, it's your turn now.
Okay, I'm ready to- You've got it. I'm ready to blow you all out of the water!
Do you think you can? No, I don't, actually.
All right, show us your flexibility! Are you ready?
I'm ready! Let's start!
All right, first up, left foot on green, with-
Sexy pose!
Right foot on yellow, even sexier!
Left hand on blue, wet cat Rissa pose!
Right foot on green, sea lion pose!
Right hand on blue, do one push-up!
Left hand on red, octopus pose!
Left foot on blue, pirate pose!
Dark breath.
Da da la la da la Dark
Ra pa pan pan pan
You will want it more, want it more
Ey! You will love it now, love it
Ra pa pan pan
風穴開けたんだ
支配は始まった
息はもう掛けたのよ
but you don't know
自覚ないはずよ
(huff-n-puff)
抑え切れない
自力制御不能な power
(power)
捕まえてみなよ
影形もない my heart
(i'm so crazy crazy in love)
半信半疑な素振りは no no
心に従って 忠実心見せてよ
今こそ baby don't let me down
Ra pa pan pan pan
(ey!)
Gotta be kidding me
クセになるでしょ?
Ra pa pan pan pan
(ey!)
No love's killing me
足りないのよ oh no... yes!
Dark Breath
感じるでしょ 革命的存在を
It's God's breath
澱んだ 感情 吹き払って
Ra pa pan pan pan
浅はかな言葉 建前 並べて
何気ないことくらい baby i know
ほら 図星でしょう?
(huff-n-puff)
枯れゆくこと 受け入れた 鮮やかな flower
(flower)
知りながら 贈る笑顔に 潜む姿
(really hate it, hate its smile)
街はべでた
The town is waiting,
導くのすべてアンソマリー
anomalies guide everything.
誰もが悩む 険教へとチェンジ
Everyone struggles, changing into a steep path.
天使の城と修道院は来た 盆栽にはデスね
The angel's castle and monastery have arrived, for bonsai trees, right?
誰でも傷つかないけど手でいれるわ
Anyone won't get hurt, but I'll get my hands on it.
からかってクスリになるでしょ
Teasing makes for good medicine, right?
のどから急に奪ってないのよ
I'm not snatching it straight from your throat.
ヤスタカフレンズ ジェネレーション
Yasutaka Friends Generation.
普通じゃないさと
Saying it's not ordinary,
いつかすべてをろっくんろーる 済ませて
someday finishing everything with rock 'n' roll.
ナパパン パパン パパン
Napapan papan papan!
ララァ
Lala...
よっしゃ！
Alright!
Are you ready?
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん？
How about it with the Paipai Mask?
未来恋の果てのこされた
Left behind at the end of future love,
出どころ不明の金山の山
a mountain of unknown origin.
あいつの気配がするものは 未練ばかりで食えやしない
Anything that feels like him is just lingering attachment, uneatable.
あたしは生きながら化けて出る 鏡の前で早変わり
I haunt this world while still alive, transforming quickly in front of the mirror.
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん？ 今宵もひと暴れ
How about it with the Paipai Mask? Rampage again tonight!
踊れ 踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance, dance,
みだれ髪はずむ胸
unkempt hair, bouncing chest.
匿名のおナに酔いしれて
Intoxicated by anonymous desire,
最初の罠に酔いしれて
intoxicated by the first trap.
shine a spot...
shine a spotlight on me now!
パイ パイ パイ パイ パイ パイ ヤッパイ
Pai pai pai, pai pai pai, yappai!
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
Paipai Mask is a multi-millionaire!
パイ パイ パイ パイ パイ パイ ヤッパイ
Pai pai pai, pai pai pai, yappai!
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar high!
ほらほら 踊れよ
Come on, come on, dance!
散財万歳 コインシャワー
Hurrah for reckless spending, coin shower!
刹那を生きろよ
Live in the fleeting moment.
瞬間クライマックス
Instantaneous climax,
浮世忘れてふける ダンスインハイ パイヤ パイヤ
forgetting the floating world in a dancing high, paiya paiya!
discotheque queen あぁ パイパイ仮面
Discotheque queen, ah, Paipai Mask!
歌は？
What about the song?
Sing this song together! What do we both have in common?
オッケー！ パイ！ パイ！
Okay! Pai! Pai!
悪い奴だと知りつつも 恋は盲目と目も無く
Knowing he's a bad guy, but love is blind and merciless.
愛のために血も青くした あたしはとんまな道化師さ
I turned my blood blue for love, a foolish clown am I.
虫籠の蝶は飛ばねばならぬ 虫ケラで終わっちまう
A butterfly in a cage must fly, or it ends up just a bug.
パイパイ仮面が解き放つ 今宵も羽ばたけよ
Paipai Mask unleashes, spread your wings tonight too!
喰らえ 喰らい 喰らえ ケダモノめ セセモノめ 求めよ さらば与えられん
Devour, devour, devour, you beasts, you freaks! Seek and you shall be given.
喰らえ 喰らい 喰らえ ゲダモノよ クセモノよ
Devour, devour, devour, you monsters, you oddities!
ゲスモノよ クセモノよ
You scoundrels, you weirdos!
パット目覚めたら あてられない
Awaking in a flash, unbelievable.
shine a spot... shine a spot...
shine a spotlight on me now!
パイ パイ パイ パイ パイ パイ ヤッパイ
Pai pai pai, pai pai pai, yappai!
パイパイ仮面はボンキュッポン
Paipai Mask has a bom-kyu-pon figure!
パイ パイ パイ パイ パイ パイ ヤッパイ
Pai pai pai, pai pai pai, yappai!
視線の先はスキャンダル
The target of gazes is a scandal.
どんどん揺らしそよ
Shake it more and more.
フラッシュアワーにバイブレーション
Flash hour and vibration,
サイケに染まれよ
get dyed in psychedelic colors!
泡立つバブルモーション
Foaming bubble motion,
一瞬でゾーンに入る ダンスインハイ パイヤ パイヤ
entering the zone in an instant, dancing high, paiya paiya!
discotheque queen あぁ パイパイ仮面
Discotheque queen, ah, Paipai Mask!
今日もあいつはどこかの国でどんなワルさしてるやら
Today too, I wonder what kind of mischief that guy is up to in some country.
あたしはいつでもあんたの港
I am always your harbor.
疲れたときには戻っておいで
Come back here whenever you're tired.
バイバイ バイバイ バイ バイバイ まわる まわる まわルーナ
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye, bye-bye, spinning, spinning, spinning Luna
バイバイ バイバイ バイ バイバイ 黄金蝶舞い上がれ
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye, bye-bye, golden butterfly, soar up
ほらほら さあ踊れよ だんだん満杯 本社は
Come on, come on, dance now, gradually packed, the headquarters
手をつなぎ 生きろよ 瞬間クライマックス
Hold hands and live on, momentary climax
浮き世よ 忘れて捨てる ダンシングハイ バイ バイ バイ バイ
Floating world, forget and discard, dancing high, bye, bye, bye, bye
ディスコティック クイーン ああ バイバイ まわる
Disco Queen, ah, bye-bye, spinning
ぐるぐる＠まわる＠まわルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning Luna
まわる まわる まわるルーナ
まわる まわる まわるルーナ ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning Luna Luna
まわる まわる まわるルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning Luna
まわる まわる 地球をぐるぐる
Spinning, spinning, spinning around the Earth
またたく間に街中が
In the blink of an eye, the town is
まわる まわる あたまクラクラ
Spinning, spinning, my head is dizzy
幕が上がり祭りの始まり
The curtain rises, the festival begins
まわれ まわれ 眉を開いたら
Spin, spin, when you open your eyebrows
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning, spinning, turn around, spinning more around
もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Turn around and around more
みんな ぐるぐるぐるぐる 回って もっと
Everyone spinning, spinning around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning, spinning, turn around, spinning more around
もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと
Turn around and around more
みんな ぐるぐるぐるぐる 踊って みんな ぐるぐる 回って
Everyone dancing around, everyone spinning around
もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと
Turn around and around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる そうやって もっと 回って
Spinning, like that, turn around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って ずっと まわルーナ
Smiling as you spin, always spinning Luna
回り過ぎたらの世界
If you spin too much, the world's
の闇が見え隠れ
darkness peeks through
する恐怖 乱舞 大丈夫
A chaotic dance of fear, it's okay
守るからまわるから
I'll protect you, I'll keep spinning
まわる地球は回り始め
The Earth started spinning
幾千年 いつまでも
billions of years ago, forever
このまま回るみんなに
Like this, bringing happiness
幸を… まわりつづく
to everyone... continuing to spin
まわルーナ ますますます
Spinning Luna, more and more
社会がぐるぐる ま～… あれ？
society is spinning... huh?
まわり 続く まわルーナ
Continuing to spin, spinning Luna
ますますます 社会がぐるぐるま
More and more, society is spinning
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning, spinning, turn around, spinning more around
もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと
Turn around and around more
みんな ぐるぐるぐるぐる 回って もっと
Everyone spinning, spinning around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning, spinning, turn around, spinning more around
もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと
Turn around and around more
みんな ぐるぐるぐるぐる 踊って みんな ぐるぐる 回って
Everyone dancing around, everyone spinning around
もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと
Turn around and around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる そうやって もっと 回って
Spinning, like that, turn around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って ずっと まわルーナ
Smiling as you spin, always spinning Luna
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning, spinning, turn around, spinning more around
もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと
Turn around and around more
みんな ぐるぐるぐるぐる 回って もっと
Everyone spinning, spinning around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って まわルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning Luna
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spinning, spinning, turn around, spinning more around
もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って まわルーナ
Turn around and around more, spinning Luna
ぐるぐる まわる まわルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning Luna
ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ ぽぽぽぽぽ
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po, po-po-po-po-po
Mayday, Mayday
mayday, mayday
Mayday 恋は届いてる
心がスキッと痛いみたい
Mayday, my love is reaching you,
though my heart aches sharply.
Baby なんて魅力的
見せるテクニック はすきにらくら
Baby, what a charming display,
a technique that makes me dizzy.
Mayday それじゃもの足りない
次にもっともっとよばるスタッフ
Mayday, that's not enough.
I want more and more staff calling out!
Hey, Hey もっとちらしてよ
あなたのこころに生えてきたいの
Hey, hey, scatter it more!
I want to sprout inside your heart.
ああ 見ず知らずの甘い罠
Ah, a sweet trap from a total stranger—
ああ ハマってあげようか
Ah, shall I let myself fall for it?
ああ 完全に感情コントロールして
きっとはずのノリ
Ah, completely controlling my emotions,
this must be the rhythm!
フラフラしちゃいそう なまいきな匂い
どこまでフラフラしちゃいそう
I might stagger, such a cheeky scent,
staggering all the way—
手を離しゃ負けじゃなくて
レイクライがじゃないもん
It's not about losing if I let go,
not a crybaby at all!
だって君の前にじゃ絶対
Help me please!
Because right in front of you,
absolutely... Help me please!
でも君の前じゃ絶対
Help me please!
But right in front of you,
absolutely... Help me please!
Mayday 舵が取れないの
気持ちがモヤっと晴れないし
Mayday, I can't steer my wheel,
my feelings won't clear up.
Baby なんてじゃいられない
瞬きの隙間もじょめじょめ
Baby, I can't stay like that,
blinking in every gap, step by step.
絶対ありわけないじゃん Can I get it?
There's no way that's true, can I get it?
あり得たかのカンチガイ
どんだいだての今野ウェザー
A misunderstanding that might have been possible,
what kind of weather is this now?
大人張りているこんな感じだって
溶け出せような太陽に身を任せろ
Acting like an adult, even feeling like this,
surrender yourself to the melting sun!
帰えりあたしじゃいけない 身を任せろ
帰えりあたしじゃないや
Can I not return as myself?
Surrender yourself, I'm not myself anymore!
燃やすミー いやいや
でもめちゃくちゃに足を奪われてんな
Burning me, no no,
but my feet are completely swept away!
奪われたってなんでもあたしじゃないわ
絶対 Let's make it!
Even if I was robbed, I'm definitely not myself!
Let's make it!
演奏して 愛は手探るだろう
Play the song, love must be
groping in the dark...
いつかは かないたリング 消えるの
Someday, the ringing will disappear...
本当は意外と単刀直入に
日替わり捨てられたけど
Actually, quite straightforwardly,
thrown away day by day, but—
君のせいで心のホログラム
Because of you, the hologram of my heart—
気付けば手を伸ばしちゃって
その先苦しくって
Before I knew it, I reached out my hand,
and beyond that, it hurts!
Give me more, give me one of that sweet love
一体 ここにいたのかい 落ち着く場所さ
Where were you all this time? It's a comforting place.
その手で触れてよ
Touch me with those hands.
鳴いてよ 狂ってよ 醜いその名に愛を伝えて
Cry out, go crazy, and bestow love upon your ugly name.
ほどいてよ ほどいてよ 鉄格子じゃあ
Untie me, untie me, inside iron bars...
Help me, help me, rescue me, rescue me
Save me, save me, mayday, don't rescue me
どんな時も一緒なら どのような君も 見も離れきっとさ 外れ出ししたんだ
If we're together no matter what, no matter what you're like, we've broken away for sure.
Don't let me down
♪
(Music playing)
You better have a freaking wonderful rest of your day because I'm monitoring you, all right?
You got it, Liz.
Thanks for the invite.
For justice!
And she's gone. Goodbye, Liz! I love you!
Good day, Nerissa Ravencroft, mother of my child, happy birthday!
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up
いかにも 鼠にも お腹 goo goo
Be that as it may, octopus or not, my stomach is rumbling
手に持つ少なめ いざ zun zun
What's left in my hands is scarce, here we go zoom zoom
飯は食わねば 寝る寝る never na
If I don't eat, I can't sleep, sleep, never na
タイム・スリーピー ya
Time sleepy, ya
ここどこ 迷子で go go go
Where am I? Lost, go go go
dancing darling
じゃんじゃん進化進行
Evolution in progress
干渉あり 人類発祥どうこう
Is there interference? What about the origin of humanity?
ァ 良い感じ そろそろ 出発進行
Ah, feels good, soon departure, forward march
去るもの追わず 猿 ぱっぱぱぷ〜
Don't chase the ones who leave, monkey, papa pi pa pu~
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up
欲しいモンはほら これだろう旦那
What I want, look, this is it, right, sir?
さあ わんわんわんわん わんっ ワンッ
Come on, bow-wow, bow-wow, bow, wow
チキチキ ワァハー！
Chitty chitty waha!
脳内 全開 yeah やっぱっぱ party
Brain full throttle, yeah, party
笑って 泣いて 踊れば あいあいあいっおー
If you laugh, cry, and dance, ai ai ah oh
パンドラ 開いて ドヴァッて 飲ませた raw
Open Pandora's box, gulped it down, raw
ごらん 遊ばせ
Please enjoy watching
あちゃちゃちゃちゃちゃちゃちゃっ パリーン♪
Ah, cha cha, cha cha, parin~
おーわっあっ アイアイ
Oh wa ah, ai ai
気分は high とんどんたん
Mood is high, don don tan
おーわっあっ アイアイ
Oh wa ah, ai ai
愛の間合い どんどんぱん
The distance of love, don don pan
つながってんだ 記録なんだ
It's connected, it's a record
gene & meme だ
It's gene & meme
連綿つむいだ 犬 猿 人 神
Spun together, dog, monkey, human, god
報酬いいんだ 働いてんだ 連勤なんだ
The reward is good, working, consecutive duty
休みなし 毎日が 月月金土 あーん
No holidays, every day is Monday, Monday, Friday, Saturday
乱心ダーウィン じゃんじゃん淘汰進行
Derangement Darwin, elimination in progress
人類抹消 あるでしょ ai 暴走
Humanity erased, AI runaway
ァ もう最深部 そろそろ 計画進行
Ah, already at the deepest part, plan execution
もうゆびゆびまで わん つっさりー
Until the Yubi Yubi, one, two, three
おらょー おらょー だんだんすやん...
Look at me, gradually falling asleep...
オーマイガ オーマイ ワイフ ようやく真理 辿り着いた
Oh my god, oh my wife, finally reached the truth
無限 螺旋 抜け 無心で
Escaped the infinite spiral, innocently
ほら ウェイ いつ ほら ウェイ いつ
Look, way, look, way
はっ！
Yes!
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up
欲しいモンはほら これだろう旦那
What I want, look, this is it, right, sir?
さあ わんわんわんわん わんっ ワンッ
Come on, bow-wow, bow-wow, bow, wow
チキチキ ワァハー！
Chitty chitty waha!
脳内 全開 yeah やっぱっぱ party
Brain full throttle, yeah, party
笑って 泣いて 踊れば あいあいあいっおー
If you laugh, cry, and dance, ai ai ah oh
パンドラ 開いて ドヴァッて 飲ませた raw
Open Pandora's box, gulped it down, raw
ごらん 遊ばせ
Please enjoy watching
あちゃちゃちゃちゃちゃちゃちゃっ パリーン♪
Ah, cha cha, cha cha, parin~
おーわっあっ アイアイ
Oh wa ah, ai ai
気分は high とんどんたん
Mood is high, don don tan
おーわっあっ アイアイ
Oh wa ah, ai ai
愛の間合い どんどんぱん
The distance of love, don don pan
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up
Let's go ahead and introduce this year's birthday merch!
Please take a look at the set.
There's also going to be a limited set that comes with an autographed postcard.
So let's take a look at all the details.
First up, can you believe it? I made a Jailbird onesie!
Isn't it so cute?
Oh, it looks warm.
It looks so comfy.
It's perfect if you want to let out your inner fat flock member.
You can wear it to sleep, you can wear it out.
Who cares? You wear wherever you want.
It's it's a kigurumi.
So do consider picking it up, please.
All right, and the next item is
the Jailbird beanie.
Do you want to look cool?
Do you want to look nonchalant while also repping the Jailbirds, repping the fat flock?
Now, you can with this beeping beanie.
It even has a Jailbird embroidery on it.
Look at the little horn.
It is so cool and cute at the same time.
And now for the third item,
y'all, look gets so cool.
As cool as ice, and might I say, the Jailbird Ice Tray!
You can make six different Jailbird ice cubes.
They're so cute, look at all those expressions too!
I can't wait to use this and put this in my matcha latte.
What do you think? What are you going to use it first in?
Uh, I don't know.
I think I'm going to put it in matcha lattes too,
but I think I could just put it in my water.
I could put it in anything.
You could just take them, you could chuck them too.
Not at people, but like at the floor.
At people would be okay too.
At people?
Yeah. No, no, no, no!
Not at people! Oh, goodness. Save us!
It's fine!
And with this, the Day-Out with Nerissa Acrylic Keychain.
You can take it along with you, take Nerissa everywhere you go, and take photos!
You know, just like uh you're uploading it to that my favorite app, Nerissa Ravencroft.
That's the best one.
Let's let's favorite app, Nerissa Ravencroft social time.
This illustration is done by my mama as well.
So it'd be awesome if you would share photos with this item on SNS using the hashtag #DateWithNerissa.
Did you just never mind.
And of course,
there's also a birthday set that includes a postcard and a bonus voice pack.
Along with these four items, only the limited edition comes with an autograph postcard.
So don't wait, get yours now for your fat flock friends!
Yes!
Now, what's this Day Out with Nerissa bonus voice pack like, huh?
You have a preview?
I guess I can tell you a little bit about it.
Well, it's actually based off of the illustration.
So, uh, it's a day out, similar to the dates that you guys came out with.
I'm going to be going on a date with the Jailbirds to an amusement park.
So you can look forward to the shenanigans that ensue.
Shenanigans! Always shenanigans. Such a grass.
Anyways, I worked really hard to come up with all this merch so that everybody could enjoy it, so be sure to grab yours as soon as it goes live. The links will be in the description.
Well, this turned out to be such a wonderful birthday!
And Advent, I'm so happy that we could celebrate all together as well. It made it so special for me.
And we also had Justice as guest, too, singing with me.
So, thank you Justice for coming and celebrating with me as well, and...
Most of all, thank you Jailbirds! Thank you everyone! Have a great day! Bye-bye!
Jailbirds, thank you for coming to my 3rd birthday here in hololive! You've truly made the last few years of my life so incredibly memorable. I can't wait to see where this next year of my life with Advent, hololive, and you takes me! Thanks for always supporting me, and let's keep doing our best!!! - Nerissa